import './blog2.css';
export const newdata = [
   {
      question: 'What is "Telemedicine?"',
      answer: 'Telemedicine is a way that doctors can deliver care to patients by using telecommuncations such as; phone or computer. Patients can get live video chats with their doctors online. ', 
   },
   {
      question: 'How do I set up a Telemedicine appointment?',
      answer: 'You will see the “Book an appointment” on the home page, where you add in your information and can schedule. ', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Will I get a reminder before my Telemedicine appointment?',
      answer: 'Yes. You will receive a reminder a week before your visit that would also ask to "Confirm Your Telemedicine Appointment", and another reminder 24hrs before your visit ', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Will I need an internet connection to access my appointment?',
      answer: 'Yes, we recommend a strong wireless connection so that your appointment goes smoothly', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Will I be meeting with a licensed doctor during my Telemedicine visit?',
      answer: 'Yes, you will. All our doctors are licensed, MDs, and will deliver quality care to you.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Can I use my insurance for my telemedicine visit?',
      answer: 'In many cases, yes.  You can fill out your insurance information before or during your scheduled appointment and a healthcare provider will inform you if your insurance qualifies for your visit.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Is there an extra cost for a Telemedicine visit? ',
      answer: 'No, there is no extra cost. We bill insurance for any visits.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Can anyone have access to a Telemedicine visit? ',
      answer: 'We require patients to be 18 years and above. Patients who are under the age of 18 must have an adult present during their Telemedicine visit.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Can I use my mobile phone for my Telemedicine visit? ',
      answer: 'Yes. The doctor will need to see you through your device. We suggest using a mobile phone or computer that has video and audio capabilities. ', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Will I need to be a pro with technology to use the Telemedicine application?',
      answer: 'No. Our Telemedicine application is very simple and patients of all ages can easily use the platform.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'What happens if I need help connecting to my appointment or running late for my appointment?',
      answer: 'Please contact us by calling 470-353-7879 ', 
   },
   {
      question: 'What if I need to speak to a healthcare provider before my appointment?',
      answer: 'We advise you contact us by calling 470-353-7879 or by filling out the "Contact Us" form on our webpage. If it is an emergency please do not hesitate to call 911', 
   },
    {
        question: 'Can I get a prescription after my Telemedicine visit? ',
        answer: 'Yes. The doctor will send any prescription needed to your pharmacy after your session is over.', 
     },
   {
      question: 'Will I have to wait a long time before I am able to get a Telemedicine visit?',
      answer: 'It all depends on the appointment calender. You can book your apppointments 2 weeks in advance.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'How will I know if Telemedicine is for me?',
      answer: 'We understand that every patient is different and Telemedicine continues to evolve. Telemedicine provides many benefits to patients such as lowering stress, having good communication between patients and doctors, it saves time and money and every immediate needs can be easily met.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'What will be discussed during a Telemedicine appointment?',
      answer: 'You can speak with your doctor about anything you would normally bring up during an in-person appointment. Any or questions or concerns, symptoms you may have.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Do I get the same type of care as the in-person visit?',
      answer: 'Yes. Our doctors are responsible for making sure that they provide equal standard of care for a Telemedicine visit as well as an in-person visit.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'How long does a Telemedicine visit last for?',
      answer: 'Each appointment usually lasts for 30 minutes or more. It could also depend on the extent of the concerns that the patient has.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'What if I wanted to cancel my appointment or reschedule?',
      answer: 'You can do this by simply clicking on the cancel button under your appointment and selecting any available date and time of your choice.', 
   },
   {
      question: 'Where do I find the report of my Telemedicine visit? ',
      answer: 'You can find your report under the "Reports" tab. You can also access your past reports from there.', 
   }
];